junkard love podcast at what age do we
learn how to have better
conversations at what age do we learn to
have better conversations with
ourselves I've forgotten in the past too
so I don't want to do that no I totally
know what you mean yeah I uh it's funny
if I start my morning and have zero
interaction with anyone then it's I
start realizing it like later on the day
I'm like wow I haven't talked to anybody
all day long that just it has a funny
effect it has a funny effect on like
your own brain sometimes you know it's
like you're very much just in your head
it's very it's it's hard to get out of
that hard to like consider like oh yeah
there's other people that like have
other cares in the world that like I'm
conversing with you know it's like
interesting too when you can tell two
people have that same kind of like day
or that same kind of like experience and
they get together and they're both kind
of like strange and internal for a
little bit and then it slowly arms up
it's like oh yeah we're humans we can
connect and that's like what we
inherently want to do it's yeah you you
meet up with someone you you realize
you're living about six miles deep
inside your own ass basically yeah yeah
completely completely just disappeared
into yourself I I like a there's this
guy I think I I might have told you
about this the other day there's this
poet David White and he has this
beautiful poem um the gist is basically
when we're living alone when we're by
ourselves we're living as a question
everything is a question we're exploring
you know our truths who we are
especially if we're listening to
philosophy or practicing meditation
we're kind of unraveling and and
questioning everything about ourselves
but when we're living with others we're
living as a statement you know totally
and and the the difference between our
two selves is like it can be so so vast
and in like I think the balance of just
being a human is trying to consistently
uh you know use the accordion of when
you meet up with somebody like stop
living as such a crazy question and try
to live as more of a statement of those
questions that you've been practicing
and I don't know it's it can
be I don't know like if someone if
someone is going into public spaces and
they're continuously living as a a
question you might after a while start
to think they're a bit loopy you know we
have to have those statement moments in
our lives too it's funny because you I
thought about this this morning and like
part of me like this morning I was like
wow I'm actually like kind of nervous
like I've never like been on like a
podcast before it's like it's a it's I
was thinking about the formats I was
like man me and Jacob talk super openly
all the time it's like very free flowing
and like very
easy and I started thinking about like
exactly what you're talking about here
which is like by living as a statement
and like I think that there's a couple
things that I that I think about that
that that I thought of this morning
which is
um living as a statement is inherent
when you're like around other people
that to do it like as a creative like as
an artist like as yourself like I have
questions for you as far as
like you're able to live as a statement
even outside of yourself even if or even
outside of interactions with others as
in like in your own internal time you're
able to live as a statement and I guess
inherently you would what I've always
heard and what you think is like when it
comes to Art when it comes to like uh
you know trying to um get in touch with
yourself trying to to show a side of you
a lot of it is for yourself but it's
interesting whenever you think about
like how much of it is for others I mean
to say that you have an intention to
like share your art and share yourself
you're now taking that internal that uh
that that thought of a question and tur
it into a statement I was thinking this
morning like part of the reason why I am
like a little nervous about getting on
here is I was like I'm not used to that
I'm not used to like sharing
um I guess in a medium that
is bigger than like who can actually
hear me right now you know what I mean
it's like I'm so used to a medium of
like hey like
maybe five people can hear me or maybe
like you know some of those like old
like meetings that float on I would
reach like 20 people or 25 people or
something like that that was always cool
but the thought of trying to reach more
than that has never been um it's never
like dawned on me and something about
that was like oh that's scary you know
um so I wonder like how do you view your
own art or your own creativity or your
own living as a statement um and bigger
than just like a real world because like
the real world is in my theory it's it's
you know I'm I'm used to like me and you
and like maybe a few other people you've
actually like performed in front of
audiences before like how much does that
change the way that you view just who
you are and the way that you're
shared that's such a cool question
um yeah man um I I
think we talked about this before you
know a lot of times we think that an
artist or a poet or a musician is like
you know like when they're in front of a
microphone performing that's that's when
they're a musician when they're a poet
but um artist kind of has
this strange Arc to it because you're
kind of intentionally always trying to
be a poet in in some ways you know
you're always trying to be an artist
like how I interface with the world in
my everyday life whether I'm with people
or not with people i' I'd like to think
that I try to bring a lens of like how
sounds so dorky really but like how
would a poet see this like what what
like how could I how could I see this
for more
deeply than than what the surface is is
kind of showing me um and and I think
that an artist or a poet or or whatever
you know when when we spend a lot of
time you know in our basements in our
basements of our minds too you know just
like spending a ton of time as a
question like we were
saying you're like digging stuff up
you're working on yourself you're
constantly learning about yourself
you're constantly like shaving off parts
of yourself you're trying things you're
you're failing you're succeeding like
consistently moving like you're not just
I'm this exact person and I play this
exact video game at this exact time
every day you know like it's a constant
shedding like a a snake shed skin and
then you go out in front of a microphone
or in front of an audience and and to
some extent you're almost saying like
all right here's what I what I've
discovered like here's here's what I've
learned about being a human you know and
like the thought of like maybe you'll
see the answer to my question the same
time that I see it like my question is
can I perform to this level in front of
this amount of people I've never done it
before let's try something new and
everyone could be like holy [__] we just
saw it and you can't or like holy [__]
we just saw it and you can and like you
both realize it at the same time I mean
almost to the extent of like think like
an athlete you know an athlete
like the thought of trying to run like
five miles you've never run five miles
before right you try to do your five
miles you make it to four you're like ah
[__] I'm going to do it tomorrow and you
try for a couple weeks or whatever and
finally you get there like wow I ran
five miles today I didn't stop I totally
did it and imagine like taking that to
the level of like I don't know say like
a marathon or even say um I don't know I
guess even like a cyclist like T to
front style style stuff where um you can
do all that in your own head and in your
own time like not in front of people the
minute you take it and put it in front
of an audience it totally changes like
this question is no longer or like this
living life as a question is no longer
just for me now it's like I'm trying to
answer my own questions and make a
statement at the same time yeah it's
like I mean that's inherently scary as
hell obviously you know it's like I
think that's why I have a lot of respect
for artists and and people like yourself
in in particular because um you are able
to put something out there that is just
so
it's bold whether it's whether you want
it to be or not like it's inherently
bold you know
um yeah I
mean I think that like you know we're
all individuals of course we have our
own individual Journeys but there's also
uh you know a togetherness of We're All
Humans too we're all having this
experience and I think that some people
regardless of you know what capitalism
has their job title ads like what they
submit on their taxes what their job
title says like a lot of us have roles
uh
roles as a community of humanity and I
think like think back you know when
Travis pada did a backflip on a
motorcycle on a dirt bike like suddenly
like he did that and it was televised it
was filmed on camera and suddenly bro
everyone's doing back flips like he just
ripped it open so he gave permission to
the other humans who are like they're
using that that route of of MX as their
way of self-expression of of of
being of just like creating something
out of nothing that wasn't there before
it hadn't been accomplished to our
knowledge um they're using you know
Motocross and second somebody does it
other people like holy [__] I get same
with the the four-minute mile one person
does it and suddenly everyone's just
smashing the finish line and now the
numbers are insane for how quickly
somebody can can uh R run a mile and I
think that when we're in the audience or
we're observers of somebody doing their
thing their art their poetry their um
there their expression of of what they
can do there's this thing in the
audience where we're like that that like
you're doing that thing that you're
you're pushing the edges of like I'm an
individual you're an individual but
together we're human you're pushing that
thing for us like as much as there's a
lot of ego involved the the person
performing there's like there has to be
this this ego of like you know you got
to amp yourself up you got to like be
the person you got to uh you know you're
you're putting on the captain's side
you're playing the role for sure but
then there's also this kind of
like lessening or or like letting go of
like I'm doing this for me in more of a
you know let let me show you what I've
learned that humans can do you know and
I don't know I think everyone in the
audience there's a thing within us that
feels not like a new bit of knowledge
but more of like a remembering of like a
uh oh yeah that's what we're supposed to
be doing like I wonder what I could do
what's my a and how am I pushing it how
am I not pushing it you know absolutely
it's funny because as you were talking
about that I started thinking I don't
know my camera I'm not like looking at
myself or whatever um I don't know what
that's called but I don't have like my
self view on because I was like if I
don't see myself it'll just be like that
much more natural of a conversation
because I was like every time I've
talked to Jacob I haven't seen myself so
why would I well enough I suppose yeah
exactly you didn't bring a mirror with
you that day your shades are not nearly
shiny enough you know they're just way
too dull but no it's like I thought
about that and like as you were speaking
just now like saying um you know how
much an ego comes into that I started
thinking about like Mitch Hedberg and
how like he would always had the
sunglasses on he had terrible stage
fright but he still had something in him
that was like I'm a funny [__]
and I need to get this [__] out there I
just don't really want to do it and like
I wonder I mean he didn't have that long
of a run right like unfortunately for
the entire world and for him um and like
how much does that play into like how
much does like he and
his desire to put his ego out there and
also like his or maybe his his UND
desire his desire to not have his ego
out there how much did that affect like
his comedy and his performance and I
wonder how much we like missed out on I
wonder how much um how different it
would be had that not been a thing you
know it's interesting to think of
performers that are
not specifically in his case I don't
know if it was like a traumatic thing or
was it just that he didn't
have his ego just wasn't there to put
him out there you know what I mean so I
think like did he have some sort of ego
death or something like that was there
was there some like we can get deep on
that but was there some reason in
particular why he did not want to put
himself out
there yeah I mean the the ego death
thing is is a fun you know convo in
itself
like I I think a lot of artists a lot of
performers a lot of the big times go
through some level of of ego death like
that that word that term is just
instantly sounds so icky you know it
sounds so
like performative in a sense but dude I
I don't know I
mean what's that saying about uh you
know the the millions of ideas that are
laying dormant in a graveyard you know
like all those people who never acted on
the on their intuitions on their
feelings on their dreams on the things
that they wanted to do you know they're
just think about all those ideas just
resting in a graveyard um I think the
ones that do it the ones that we see are
are the ones that they followed that
intuition they followed that like edge
of I mean I I I don't know like like
where does a guy like Mitch Hedberg end
up if he doesn't listen to that
intuition if he doesn't get himself on
stages how many Mitch Hedberg are there
out there right now yeah and are they
screaming at passing cars at a bus stop
because they've lost their minds because
they're not listening to that thing you
know it's it's
a
we we love to take credit for Stuff like
we love
to like like I think that there's
there's a way in which I didn't really
choose and I know it sounds so corny
like I didn't choose to be a musician I
didn't choose to be a DJ I didn't choose
to be a poet I didn't choose to be an
artist it's like like it's just like
what else am I going to do you know it's
like my my specific experience here my
internal dialogue tells me these certain
things and then I make the decision or I
like act on them or I don't it's like
like I don't have the like my my
internal dialogue isn't telling me like
Jake you got to cut hair bro you were
born to cut hair you were born to be a
barber and like I can't stand to walk by
someone with a bad fade I can't think of
anything else like that's not my path
mine is is is words and like I'm I'm
kind of a terrible musician but I like
love music so much that I've just like
it's all I think about it's all I try
I'm just like continuously failing and a
lot of this stuff but it's it's what my
internal dialogue is communicating to me
you know it's and you know I think in
some way we're all an expression of
what our internal dialogue is trying to
get out of us you know like some people
is is the way I talk about being an
artist and a poet and like I've got to
do this and express myself some people
that it's just motherhood it's just them
being a fantastic mom and then there's
other people where they might even have
kids but like this they'll tell you you
know I've never really had a calling
like yeah I like being a mom but like I
didn't really have that feeling of I'm
destined to be a mother you know all
talked to we've all talked to women who
have that so I just think that everybody
it's a matter of getting in tune with
what's really going on in like stepping
outside of our ego for a minute to where
we can almost like practice what we got
to do and then we get on a stage or in
front of a mic and that's where we're
living as the statement of our ego you
know that's where like the ego has to
exist you don't just get rid of it you
don't kill it that's not a real thing
you don't you don't your ego doesn't die
you just become aware that you have an
ego and then you
observe how you're fueling it how you're
a slave to it how it's moving you how
you can move it how you can use it as a
tool how it uses you as a tool you know
it's a I think the process of being an
artist of any form is a journey of
self-discovery and you'll continually
shed layers of yourself and sometimes
that's on stage sometimes you do it in
your basement and then you perform it on
stage but um it's like you know the the
the actualized being the
self-actualization the you know the
dangerous word Enlightenment uh
like an artist is I mean sorry but like
if they're worth any any shits they're
going to go down that path like I don't
know how you can be an artist and never
turn your attention on itself and go
like who am I and what am I doing you
know absolutely to me that seems like
it's the same thing like my artist
Journey and me expressing those are
my spiritual journey and I'm sharing it
out out
loud totally totally now it makes me
question it makes me question how much I
look at like my own
um my own ego in a way you know because
the thought
of the thought of like not wanting to be
in touch with it the thought of like
wanting to be like better than it or
almost like being able to look down on
your own ego and be like Oh I'm aware of
it I can see it I'm separate from it I
don't think being separate from it is a
reality you know like to say you like an
ego death I think that's just like the
realization that like you kind of suck
and like everybody else you know and
that's not a bad thing to have it's like
you can't just run around like being 22
and Invincible your entire life although
we probably know some folks that are
like that you know and it's like the
classic um phrase like that guy's just
never had his ass kicked or whatever you
know only out here that just act wild
nonstop like there's probably some
politics like that but either way it's
um the thought of like having so much
separation from it is is kind
of
unrealistic um the I think what I found
that I learned the most about myself and
like the way that I move through life
and the way that I view the world is by
becoming super duper in tune like with
my ego and like what my desires are what
my drives are why do I judge myself
where are these judgments coming from
you know what did that look like what
did that look like your initial opening
to that like when you first like I mean
even stumbled across the word ego or you
first kind of got into anyia this sort
of like spiritual stuff for you
personally like what what kind of
started you on that path and I guess
like just what did it look like at the
beginning you know I think I knew at
some point point that I was like just
not happy just like I had a lot of anger
issues when I was a child you know my
dad was uh not a great uh role model
when it came to like self-control and
anger and things like that and so I kind
of I've always I always kind of knew
that you know I kind of knew that I
could fly off the handle really easily
and like this is talking about when I
was like you know teens right and uh at
some point I met a girl um you know
first love kind of thing and she got me
into like a lot of uh just like
self-help stuff you know and it's
probably a combination of of a bunch of
things happen at once one being like
finding my way outside of like like say
like a we'll call it like Rebellion
Rebellion against like the The Authority
which was like parents and like school
and all the traditional um means of this
is what you have to do every day right
and then I found my way into like work
and I found work that was um gratifying
in a lot of different ways and I found
that like work ethic and my hard work
and just my desire to
hustle um I just wanted to make a lot of
money so that I had a lot of money to
spend with all my friends and all my
cars and all my projects and things like
that and so um I started diving deep
into just going heart finding whatever I
could that would just make decent money
and um I just wanted to be the best at
everything that I could do you know um
so there's a combination of that
so like finding um I guess you would
call that like
finding
um I guess selflove finding finding
self-love and finding
um answering those questions you're
answering those internal questions and
learning about yourself and saying holy
[__] I'm better than I thought I was and
it's like to do that on a regular basis
and become like a master of your craft
even if it's serving [__] tables or
even if it's sweeping a floor you know
um probably the first time I ever
meditated was I was a janitor at a
machine shop and uh we worked on like we
had all these uh massive tools we're
working on like lays and um Mills and
things like that and it had this like
lenium floor that was in like every
cafeteria from like 1994
through like that lenium that was like
yellow before even got Sun damaged and
like mud trapped on it and things yes
yeah completely and uh they're all like
12 by 12 like one one one foot by one
foot tiles right and for whatever
[__] reason this guy set up a machine
shop in a place that had that and not
like a stained concrete just like a
concrete floor and so it would in a
machine shop you have all this like
lubricating oil like all these fluids
everywhere there's metal shavings going
everywhere everything's dirty
everything's always being cleaned so
that it can be welded everything's
always being uh cut down and you always
need the oil to do it all the oil burns
and it turned into this almost like when
you caramelize onions and your oil just
burns in your pan and it's that much
harder to clean it's kind of like that
all over the place all the time there's
just shreds of metal everywhere right
and so I was uh I got hired as a janitor
there and the reason why is because I
was I was huge in the cars and one of
the guys that worked there was also huge
in the cars we're on some Forum called
Texas racing scene from like 200 I don't
know eight or nine or something it is
how we all get together and go Street
RAC and that was what I was into you
know so this guy was like Hey we're
hiring if any of you guys are just like
you know need some whatever job um you
know this guy I knew him he had like
clout on the internet because he had
badass motorcycles and badass cars and
[__] like that I was like well I want to
go hang out with this guy I'm G find out
he sucked but the guy that worked at the
Machine Shop was awesome the guy that
own it um so long story short I started
getting into like meditating and doing a
lot of breathing exercises because I was
just getting so [__] baked like after
everybody left um that I would uh
everybody would leave the shop at like 3
o'clock and I would scrub the floors I'd
scrub those little lolium one by one
tiles and I would get super freaking
high and just like scrub and I started
like I just wanted to like make it be
the most efficient like
um it didn't even matter how fast it
went I just wanted to like do it very
effectively right and so I started doing
like basically like a wax on wax off
like I had like a certain amount of
counts for every tile that I scrubbed
and then I'd like moved to the next one
it was like very methodical and it was
like because I was so stoned I got
really [__] into it it was just fun
know and then I like I started like
focusing on my breathing and thinking
like well I better like breathe right if
I'm going to do this you know I better
like make sure I've got my breathing
like in control so that I know exactly
like how many tiles I'm going to knock
out on this row before I move the next
and how many Strokes of the of the the
scrubber and you know whatever whatever
else so that's probably like the very
first time I started getting in touch
with like my ego um because I started
realizing that I was getting a lot from
that I was getting a lot from the work
then I started thinking about like I
mean I was in a relationship so I
started thinking about like my
girlfriend like awareness around like
what it means to be in love and what it
means to like have all these you know
desires and like I never had I was kind
of like a light bloomer you know I was
like 18 or 19 in my first relationship
had never lost my virginity before then
or anything like that and so it was kind
of interesting to like be going through
all these like very transformational
like life changes all at the same time
with the coupling of like meditation and
like at the time I didn't really know it
but like I was like teaching myself
breath work um and I was just kind of I
was doing what I had learned in like
high school band luckily I had like a
band instructor that was huge into
breathing exercises and he taught us
about like how I can help you focus and
that kind of transitioned into that um
that janitorial job
so um yeah to answer your question I
think I first started um getting
into self-actualization and um the ego
and and things like that at you know the
age of like 19 or so when I was
scrubbing floors at a at a machine shop
that's so cool man I was just thinking
about like visualizing you scrub on
these floors and you may not there may
not be a direct answer for this what do
you think it is why did you want to do a
good job rather than just get the job
done I think that is like one of those
like nature verse nurture questions um
it probably has a lot to do with nurture
um it probably has a lot to do with
um just like I I got a lot of work work
ethic from like the people around me
both my parents were entrepreneurs they
both worked really [__] hard all the
dinner table conversations were like
like you know my dad was an architect
and my mom was a permit expeditor and
like they actually my dad got her into
business and they realized they couldn't
work together but they still were in the
same business so they were like always
throwing business back and forth between
each other they always had the similar
clients um and they I saw my parents you
know we went from um you know at one
point my Mom stole or my U my sister
stole all my underwear and um just like
threw it away just as a [__] joke
which is sick and uh I was like 12 or
whatever we were super [__] poor and
uh my
mom my mom lost it she was like I have
no money for your underwear where's it
at she's screaming at me running around
I'm like I don't [__] know where it's
at I'm personally I'm like I don't
really need it you know like what do I
need that Mom I'm fine I've been wearing
underwear this whole week she is just
losing it on me and like every day I
almost feel like it was a you know what
now that I'm remembering it they stole a
lot of it and then they realized how
funny it was they stole it all so it was
like a you know was a multifaceted
approach to this and it was it was
really just it was a dark dark time for
me but it was it was hilarious it was
really funny so they stole all my [__]
and so um my mom uh we were so poor that
she couldn't buy me underwear and so for
like a month I just didn't wear
underwear and then finally like I don't
know if she got it at Goodwill or what
but she got like some really cheap under
some hamy down undies bro
I almost feel like she got me like
little boy shorts and just like made me
wear those or something as box or briefs
um but I gu what I'm trying to get out
here is like we were really poor and um
I saw us when we moved here we moved to
Austin in 1996 um broke is a joke um
they both just like started up shop they
didn't have income they just had some
savings they literally moved here as
like refugees from Sacramento just like
the crime in Sacramento got too bad and
and business dealings went the wrong way
from my dad long story like basically it
was just a bad place for them to be so
when they opened up shop in Austin it
was like starting from nothing with
three kids um and like no real Community
we didn't have anybody here I don't I
still to this day don't really know why
we moved to Austin it might have just
been like my dad was like we're going
there there's money there you know like
very like he's born in 1935 it's like a
very like old school like way of
thinking about that right so um yeah I
watched them go from like not having
money to underwear to like one day in
Middle School my mom like picks me up
from school in alexas and I was like
what the [__] is going on here Mom yeah
it was really crazy to see it really
really really crazy were you aware of
like when you were that age were you
aware of you know the economics of
things were you aware like oh we're were
kind of a a lowincome family were were
were poor like did you have those
dialogues within yourself
not really I knew that my friends had
more like quite a bit like I knew like
we moved into like
a I wouldn't call it upper middle class
I wouldn't call it lower middle class I
would call it a perfectly [__] middle
class neighborhood um we leased the
house or rented it whatever um and
everybody else in the neighborhood
bought it we didn't know that until
later on but um my buddies that I met
you know one of them his dad is like a
tech engineer my other buddy uh his dad
was a um
excuse me was a president at like a
Frost Bank both of them had like big
two-story houses both of them had like
big SUVs or like fans they take on road
trips and trucks and we moved there we
had two identical 1993 era Toyota Previa
minivans that both had over 200,000
miles on I'm so glad two of the same van
I thought it was so weird like it's
still so weird like why move on your
parents end to be I was and like still
to this day like I remember they sold
one of them to this lady and like she
drove it until like a few years ago
seemingly like probably like 800,000
miles you know like the original OG
Toyota you know people talk about the
truck but the minivan is where it's at
um but no so like we had these minivans
and like my dad like sold one of them
and bought a Buick and it was like an
old Buick and we called it the roach
mobile because every time you sat on the
seats roaches are WR it was so bad it
was so so we we knew that
like I think my sister my sister was
older than me by like five years she
knew that something was up and so me and
my two siblings kind of like caught on
you know what I mean but we didn't
realize we were like [__] broke as a
joke we're still having a great time you
know we had buddies with more money it
was cool hanging out with them because
their parents probably felt bad for us
they take us to dve and Busters you know
what I mean so it kind of weird like
thinking back on it now I'm like wow
that's actually pretty [__] weird
um but uh no at the time we had no idea
we just thought it was you know regular
life I suppose yeah yeah but do it's
interesting like how our view as a child
influences what we do later on in life
like the there's there is a storyline
that your parents could have also
followed of like never taking the move
to Austin never like they could have
been making the exact same amount that
year that they're making now you know
like totally I think there's a move you
know I mean kind of I'm I'm stretching
to really relate it back to what we're
talking about with like ego death and
stuff I think there is a move of
noticing hey here's the hand that I was
dealt but I'm G to draw some more cards
or I'm G to like get a new hand you know
like I I think some of us can go our
whole lives just feeling like Fate has
handed us a certain hand of cards and
those are the only ones we can play you
know I think um
I think the statistics could probably
speak for themselves the amount of
people that you know we kind of grow up
and we end up making we're in the
same same class economically as our
parents you know like we end up making a
similar like like if I had poor parents
for me to grow up and suddenly be rich
is like really a a feet like I I had to
notice and look around and go okay you
know if I do only what I was taught or
if I only play the hand I was dealt I'm
probably going to end up in these
positions I am instead going to actively
notice that bring awareness to that and
choose to to learn something new or do
different things and try to route my own
path so um absolutely I think there's a
little bit of that within ego death
right of like almost I guess just to
really stretch the analogy of of playing
a new hand of cards of like
noticing here's a path I could take and
this one's already laid out for me and I
don't have to do much to do this one but
there's this voice inside of me that
really wants me to try this idea or like
go talk to that person or there's that
corporation that for whatever reason I
feel like I could work there and I'm
going to go find out who the boss is and
find his email and send him an email and
I'm going to go like try to talk to him
at the Starbucks or you know like these
little things where we just we see
ourselves somewhere like I think that I
can do that even though I don't think
that I was built for that like my you
know I didn't come out of the factory
ready for this I you know I wasn't the
mold of my life doesn't seem to be
exactly made for this but I'm pretty
sure I can do it that right there is
just that's what being a human is about
you know like seeing more for ourselves
and wanting it and and actually taking
steps to to try those things absolutely
there's something to be said about um to
relate to that there's something we said
about um a phrase I heard a long time
ago from um like a mentor of mine was uh
humans emerg through emergency and it's
the idea that like the the
motivations nowadays
I don't know if I want to go into the
whole into all that or not a whole like
another realm nowadays I feel like um a
lot of the motivations that I am
currently faced with is
um I don't have anything that's like an
emergency I don't have anything that's
like around the corner um that's going
to like crush me I don't have any I
don't have any
um responsibilities I don't have any
dependence I don't have dogs I don't
have kids I don't have wives things none
of those things are pushing me to be
bigger or better than I currently am so
all the motivation that I have to find
in myself is either through like trauma
Andor like the opposite of that right
which is like I feel like that's always
a great motivation to say I'm I know
this and it's terrible and it's the
worst thing that's ever happened to me
and I never want to have that for myself
again so I'm going to do the opposite in
every way to get everything besides that
right which I feel like that's a lot of
people's motivation at the end of the
day they're motivated by the opposite of
their experience traditionally like a
bad experience right but the other side
of that is like being motivated by
something that's happened to you
happening to you currently that is just
so I mean I guess it is still trauma
it's so unbearable like the thought of
like my parents having three kids and
not being able to like feed them and
having to like ask family for money and
having deing businesses in a city where
everyone just wants to rob you all the
time like at that time Sacramento was
having a really bad gang problem a lot
of Asian gangs are moving and there's a
lot of like Rob is like early 90s you
know you're talking about post um ellot
riots and Rodney King all that I mean
pretty crazy time to be on the west
coast in general um and so I mean
there's a lot going on out there and so
for them they were motivated
by we we've got to do better we've we've
got to do something for our kids like we
are we are [__] where we're at right
now and I think moving to Texas was very
much
like if I had to guess and now I'll call
my mom later today and find out because
I'm so curious now but if I had to guess
it
was Cedar Park is the fastest growing
suburb in the country Austin has a lot
of great things going on for it like
they saw like exactly where they wanted
to be by the numbers and I think they
were just like f it we're going to move
there and uh we don't know anybody there
but we know that we can get in business
there and we know that there's
opportunity there so we're going to do
that you know it's it's weird
because my dad was born in
1935 you used to move around a lot for
opportunity you had to you didn't have
the internet you didn't have
um you didn't have like the social
interaction that we have today where
like we can just apply for a job and
like do something online you can't just
like create work out of nowhere you had
to to go find a job or you had to go
find people that were willing to pay you
for what you did and if it wasn't
working where you were at you had to
[__] leave you had to go somewhere
where that yeah that's not an issue that
we really have to deal with anymore um
at least not in our society
uh people lately like a lot of the
movement that we've seen in the US is
not because of lack of opportunity but
more of like they just want to you know
you want to move out of LA and you want
to move out of um all of California
because you want to be a some people say
it's a political Refugee some people say
it's because everything is too expensive
uh but the reality is like you could
keep your same job and go live somewhere
else and have double the house for half
the money and not pay state income tax
right yeah you want to go somewhere
where you actually have like a freedom
to go uh go for a hike on a at a park
that is not overrun by people right you
want to get out of a city that has been
plagued by lockdowns and by um Co
protocols like people moving out of New
York City and things like that I mean
you've seen a lot of exoduses from
things like that but it's not so much
because there's an opportunity somewhere
else it's more of like they've already
found the opportunity they just want to
leave because they're getting away from
um they want to have more freedom you
know which I think is super interesting
it's interesting to see um the
differences there the differences
of of uh
of of how we used to how we used to uh
move about the country to now you know I
don't know where I was going that I
don't know how much that ties into there
but no no I love I feel like it ties
ties into I mean that's the fun thing
about a podcast is it could just really
like dig in and out wherever it's it's
so fun I feel like podcasts always
you're like oh you're really over far in
here and then you bring it right back
around and everything seems
yeah conversation we've had
honestly yeah no yeah the last the last
good combo we had um we I and I could
edit this out if you don't want me to
incriminate you incriminate you but we
ate a handful of shs and just talked for
six hours
and it was just a beautiful conversation
um it was bad it was like there was so
many parts of it that I was scared of
like where's it gonna go next and then
it would just pop up like wow there it
is yeah yeah but dude I mean a lot of
times if you're trying to plan things or
overly structure them you get in your
own way I mean like we've talked about
this with podcast I just had a meeting
with with someone who's starting talking
about her own podcast and um she kind of
asked me like what do you do note wise
you know when you're interviewing
someone like how do you know what
questions to ask them blah blah blah and
I told her I was like so for one for
this this podcast you're you're my
friend and I wanted to free flow I don't
have any notes like I mean I have my
like these are notes that have nothing
to do with this podcast but I on
otherwise if it's my first or you know
first few times meeting somebody they
just wrote a book they sent me their
book they want me to interview them
about like whatever their skill is all
the page of notes um and a lot of times
they're just like it's more of the act
of writing the notes before the podcast
or the night before that kind of helped
me wrap around it but during the convo I
end up just being there with them and
like the notes are a rip cord if I need
to like shoot I'm drawing a blank I can
tell they're finishing their sentence I
don't know what to say I'm gonna look at
my notes but most part well you never
know like I mean if you've never like
even conversed with someone before so
you read their book you can read all
about them but if you've never like had
that oneon-one and like obviously like
we have this screen here you know like
that is a whole yeah that's a whole
thing that like it complet I'm not going
to say it kills your experience by any
means but it does like it definitely
changes
um it just changes the the the
naturalness whatever you want to call it
like how free flowing the conversation
can be um there there's things that are
actually there's variables that become
more sensitive over Zoom um if we're
sitting face to face in person like if
we're s sitting out you know we're at
that Airbnb there's like a beautiful
River next to us there's there's bugs
there's wonderful scenery I could be
talking with you and like looking around
and you wouldn't for a second falter you
would just like we're all here but in
Zoom we could be talking and you're
listening intently and suddenly I'm like
looking over my shoulder or I'm like
setting a text or I'm like like the
engagement is easier to unhook on Zoom
I've noticed um and I I just try to
treat that with the delicacy that it
deserves um sometimes it's you know it
comes with being the producer in
everything of the the podcast you're
hosting like I I can't say hey Jamie
pull this up or you know like hey bright
brighten my Iris like I'm the one also
doing that so I'm being the the one
who's running the podcast as I'm the the
host or the performer whatever but um um
anyway before I forget I'm sorry I like
brought us off on this side quest I I
was
curious how old so how old were your
parents when they had you and I'm
curious do you think that influenced you
to have a different perspective on the
world I mean there's this corny saying
of of being an old soul you know I'm
sure you've heard that but like I feel
like you're definitely an old soul I
feel like your perspective on on things
uh can qualify as the old sness um I
don't know do you oh I think you mind
have froze are he still there no it
seems good now good stuff well I'll just
reiterate the question so yeah totally
curious what what age were you uh what
age were your parents when had you and
then I I guess like how did how do you
think that kind of affected your life I
mean you probably growing up the kids
your age probably had different aged
parents than you did
right totally yeah totally and yeah to
say you mentioned um you kind of
consider me like an old soul and like
it's I've always felt more comfortable
around older folks anyway like I have a
bunch of uh half siblings I'm one of
like I think I'm one of 10 siblings um
and so I've got two blood siblings like
full full
blooded
whatevers my two sisters um who I've
got yeah and uh but then I've got um
what is that three then I've got got
seven other siblings um and so a lot of
them are older so like they were always
around it was very much like my dad was
really good at keeping the family
together and like very much like was The
Matriarch that kept everyone coming
around and he was the glue of the family
right and so a lot of holidays we had um
lots of siblings around and lots of uh I
mean they were all shoot they're all 20
30 years older than me so I think right
now my oldest sibling is like uh 64
years old right and I'm 33 so um what is
that he's uh 31 years older than me so
um for to say that uh I had a different
experience than a lot of you know my
friends a lot of other people my age is
completely freaking true completely true
so my dad was 56 I believe when he you
know whenever I was born um so let's
pause for just a second there is a lag
I'm now noticing yeah so to go back to
uh my experience growing up with a with
an older parent so my parents were uh 20
years apart so my dad was born in 35 and
my mom was born in 55 um so pretty big
age uh age Gap I think they met like my
mom was 30 something and he was 50
something so um but yeah growing up uh
with with an older parent I didn't
realize it was weird until I did kind of
thing you know you know it was just
normal
until like you know and even like when
people are in their 50s and
60s he aged pretty well he didn't really
look like he was super old until he was
in his 70s I would say but then like I
started realizing like oh wow all my
buddies parents are like not that old
like this guy is definitely way older
and so um yeah I would
say the difference
was the difference wasn't realized until
I was older in my ears right but a lot
of it was like I was raised like if you
think about
it half of me or half of my experience
is maybe even more than half just
because of like uh the nature of the way
that uh the family unit um
was uh created for his generation so
generation was that actually I don't
know like what the generation was CU I
think he was pre-baby Boomer 1935 is
like pretty early on you know yeah so my
mom could have been like his daughter
you know like she's 20 years younger
than him right so for me to be my mom's
daughter or my mom's son um is because
weird here man yeah yeah yeah right so
it's interesting because I'm technically
like two generations
maybe even in some Realms three
generations away from my dad meaning
that whenever you look at generations of
people in the way that they're raised in
the way that like say like you know
Generation X and Y and whatever we want
to call it they're raised by the reason
why they are dubb that generation is not
just because of the way that they were
brought up in like a um a pop pop
culture uh kind of like uh geopolitical
Norm sense it also has everything to do
with their parents and how their parents
are raising those children so their
parents experience as children generally
um I would say that basically everybody
in the world has some sort of trauma to
do with their upbringing and when they
raise their children they don't want it
to be the same and it's interesting to
say that sometimes they end up being the
exactly the [__] same as their
parents and sometimes they end up being
the exact opposite so if you think about
it in those terms um I am really just
the opposite of my dad's upbringing from
like the [__] 30s and 40s right and
I'm also the opposite of my mom's
upbringing of like the 60s and 70s right
or 50 or 50s and 60s essentially um so
I'm like a weird mut of these two
generations I don't really fit into like
a genin why or whatever what is our
generation do you know cuz you're were
born in 1994 I think or 1993 1991 but
Millennial regardless you're in 1991 I
just think you're it's messed up um we
can edit that
out don't show my age wait what are you
90 93 91 yeah 91 you're 91 oh yeah we're
both 91 yeah okay that's right so what
is our generation do we have any idea um
we're Millennials
we yeah okay so I don't know the exact
cut I think the exact cut off is like
like 80 9 or 88 or something I don't
know I know I'm Millennial that's all I
know okay so we are millennials but
I like in some in a lot of ways I was
raised as a millennial but then in a lot
of other ways I was raised with values
and traditions and morals um of a
generation that would Place me more in
like
a basically like in like the 60s to 7s
era does that make sense yeah alth
Boomer Millennial yeah it's very [__]
weird it's very [__] weird um because
like if I didn't hold a door open for a
lady I would literally get
smacked like things like that or like um
I was taught
that uh the dinner table is always to be
set with like every setting you know
like we set the dinner table every
single night had dinner together every
single night The Simpsons was always on
mind you um but
uh we always had dinner together if we
missed dinner it basically meant you
weren't going to eat maybe for that
night and the night the morning after um
I was taught to like I had to like help
the family business there was no like
when I got done with school I went home
and like we were always I mean mostly me
I was a man of the house I was the only
boy so um yeah I was always uh fixing my
dad's computers and the fax machine and
the modem and I would build all his
offices I would go with him to like
summertime was not summer camp
summertime was I went to work with my
parents and generally it was like I w't
working in the field but it was like I
was going to um help him measure up
buildings I was going to help him he had
me like fire contractors when I was like
14 years old like weird stuff like that
where I'm like I don't can you imagine
being fired by your boss's 14 year old
and like not for not for nothing but
like my BOS my dad was like the
architect of aob website which is like
very not the boss right so he would go
in and he would just like take up the
Reigns and just start like calling the
shots on [__] he was just he loved that
he he thought he was just in charge of
everything so he would go in there and
he'd fire people that didn't work for it
it was crazy and like half the time they
listen to him they're like well I guess
I'm fired I don't know that was but we
should do that more often we should
start go to job sites that we don't work
at and firing people just to some chaos
see what happens
like this is really wild right you're
done for the day yeah sorry Steve sent
me down here he said he said you're done
for the day man sorry I go home so
that's not gonna happen no no you're out
of here you're out of here Buster yeah
well man it's it's really interesting I
I thanks for elaborating on that I just
think it's so interesting to think of
like the things that you were taught
your childhood and then I mean you
mentioned you grew up you know you're
going to get a smack in the back of the
head for not holding a door open for a
lady and I totally hear that but then we
also now live in this world of
and it's not it's not for the most part
I'll say really like I'm not going to
let the internet paint how reality
really is for the most part every woman
is is every person is grateful you hold
the door open but there is this like
small percentage more and more of like I
can hold the [__] door open for
myself like I'm not lady like treat me
as a human not a lady like there there's
kind of is a you know a changing
dichotomy so it's interesting to think
of like you were given these morals and
values but you're also around people who
are similar to our age that um you know
and a little younger than us are the
generation under us more and more uh is
not used to those Traditional Values
like there sometimes those Traditional
Values they come from a place of being
sweet and kind and like helpful but
they're almost offensive now to some
like the same act could be somewhat
offensive so um I don't know I think um
I wanted to relate it back to like what
you you were talking about earli about
um you know you don't have kids you
don't have um like your responsibilities
quote unquote are kind of like they can
be self-centered like you're kind of
responsible for yourself and that's
about it um and I think about that a lot
too is like like I'm at a point where
like I want kids and I want a wife and
these things like I I want something to
like push behind me and like remind me
that I need to not focus on my dang self
so often you know or like these things
that I want to do and what I think is
important and so I almost want I almost
want the responsibilities to like take
my hands off the reins and so like I
just do what I know I need to do rather
than what I want to do you know
sometimes so anyway um I don't know if
that Sparks anything for we can make all
kinds of problems for ourselves that
like the reality is that like all all of
our problems are relative to like all of
our other problems so it's like the
problem of like oh I woke up and I
expected it to be a rainy day and now
it's too hot and I don't want to read a
book now it's like that's not a problem
if like your child has colic and you
stayed up for the last three days and
your wife is like ready to leave you
because she's like I don't think I can
hand this and we can't pay our mortgage
and now I can't even sleep work and I'm
caring about the fourth draft of some
poetry that I wrote like you know yes
yes problems are different it is wild
it's wild like even like the generations
of trauma change throughout your
experience like everyone's trauma
is the worst thing that's ever happened
to anyone is just as equal as the worst
thing that's ever happened to anybody
else so like whether you're born in the
in Compton and you learned that you only
need to sell drugs and you were burned
with cigarettes when you were a kid and
like you dropped out of school at age
seven and you are just a gangster right
and you have whatever Trauma from that
if that is your trauma or if
you're Donald's Trump daughter and you
got EXC commed from a communicated from
a family and you went from like having
millions at your disposal to now you
only have like hundreds of thousands at
your disposal your trauma is both equal
unfortunately for of us to be like
that's [__] but it's still equal you
know what I mean so like yeah I mean
your trauma of like not being able to
finish that fourth uh paragraph or or
the fourth draft of that poem is just as
bad as like your baby having colic and
your wife would it leave you you know as
as far as like a dayto day goes I
suppose yeah yeah i' see uh for every
listener who has a child and they're
just yelling at their uh at their
listening device right now like how dare
you compare me raising a child to you
trying to finish a line of
poetry I hear for you um but yeah I mean
it really is
like I I love I feel that's one of the
more important things of it's so easy to
like compare ourselves and make
ourselves a victim but like dude that is
a profound thing for everyone to learn
is like the worst thing you've ever
experienced is the worst thing you've
ever experienced the worst the like the
the most pain that you've ever gone
through there's no reason to really
compare it to the worst pain someone
else has gone through like there it's
just different problems you know like
like my pain my level nine pain is me
you know hungry when I was a teenager
someone else's level n pain might be
literally their XBox being taken away
and I know that sounds so cheap but like
so so I dated um I had the opportunity
to date a girl um who who had a child
recently and like I had to learn a lot
like I haven't spent a lot you know I'm
nieces and nephews but I live far away
like I don't really spend a ton of time
with kids and um I I got like it was I
learned a lot in you know just those
like four months of just watching her
you know she wants you know a bottle of
warm milk before bed and she doesn't get
it and so she starts to become like so
stressed out and then she's screaming
it's unreasonable right like like me you
know I have all these years of
experience like I know it's not
reasonable like the way for you to get
that thing of milk is not to scream I
know that but to her dude she's learning
about being a human and learning about
her emotions it really is the end of the
world for her at that moment and it it
was really cool for me to
like you know watch how like I want to
control the situation like I you know I
don't want her uh you know I have a
reaction my body has a reaction to her
yelling her being uncomfortable or
whatever you know but she's just a
little girl there's also this separate
reaction of going like oh yeah she's
just just how I was when I was I was
that age she's learning what it is to
like be without something that you want
and it like really sucks doesn't it and
it takes you years to really go like
okay I want that thing and I don't get
it and that's okay you know but but the
the learning process of being a human
like you know it's it's it's in stages
and it's it's all a different um bag
full of goodies that were handed and and
sometimes we can be still 25 30 years
old and we're just still kind of pissed
that we're not getting our warm milk
before bed and like it still hurts you
know like it's it's it's an act of of of
learning to like be okay with these
things um yeah going like let me ask you
like for your experience like as a child
and growing up cuz I'm sure they had to
like made you think like just dealing
with or just uh not even dealing with
but just being around and being subject
to raising a child you know how much did
that remind you of your experience as a
child and like your own parenting and
was there anything that jumped out at
you that was brought up in the sense of
like I definitely want to do this
differently from my parents or wow um
now I kind of see that they were just
humans too you know maybe this is I
guess was there anything that made you
think back to your experience as a child
and that would shape the way that you
view um parenting or or ideal parenting
in your own shoes I feel like you need
to start your own podcast this is such a
good question uh I like all of your
questions have been so good so far man
uh I feel like all of our conversations
you always have good questions bro thank
you um thanks man I appreciate yeah I
you know it's interest so I feel like
when I reflect back on my childhood I
think that was really loud to me and
this is something that's um common with
with the personality types like the mbti
um INFJs that's what I am as an
infj
um I'm not going to stop you now but can
we link to that later talk about that
later oh yeah yeah I I'll send you the
thing I'll include it for anybody
listening if you want to check that out
if you've never done your personality
type I'll put a link to the the one I
like in the description as well um yeah
so so a commonality like you can go on
the Reddit subreddit and it'll be a
common thing uh when I was when I was
younger I kind of had this awareness of
like yes I'm a part of the family but
I'm also watching the family I feel like
I was like you know we're all sitting on
we're all sitting in the living room
watching The Simpsons we're watching TV
but I also had an awareness of I'm
watching the family watch the TV and uh
it after a while I started to realize
that like not not everyone around me had
that sort of like sense of things um and
so so so something that gets me and
something that stands out to me is when
we do things and we all do it you know
so this this specific example um the
girl that I was dating for a while um
her child was you know around three or
four and what you do when the child is
in the room is you're talking about
adult things and you you say her she she
wants this like you're talking about
this child who's right here and what's
something that was really loud to me is
like when I was younger I was really
aware of those conversations and I would
always be like why are they talking like
I'm like I'm not right here like it was
always really confusing like we're
having this separate story line about me
when I'm not right here like it was
really confusing for me to continuously
extrapolate outside of what we're
actually doing and talk about what we're
doing as if I'm not there but then the
next instant I need to be paying
attention to what you say to me about me
this is about I need to follow
directions like what you know that that
was a very confusing thing um and so I I
think that I tried to you know I'm sure
I probably failed with this but I W with
this girl that I was dating I tried to
like include her daughter on everything
that was happening whatever I was doing
even if it's an adult conversation that
she doesn't know what I'm talking about
I'm still going to explain it to her I
like she I don't think she has to
understand all the words that I'm saying
or like I don't have to answer the wise
of everything like she's still even
learning how to communicate herself and
put words together and speak but I I
felt that like just saying what I'm
doing out loud including her made this
we situation um that I I have no I guess
that was something that was really loud
to me was was the absolutely
separateness when I was younger it
really really threw me off I didn't get
why people did that it was really
confusing and I don't think that they
got why they did it a lot of times I'm
like are you are you people even aware
that you're doing this like in in the
answer is
no completely it s i mean that to me the
immediate reaction that I have when you
saying that is like you were forced to
grow faster to grow up quicker than
maybe other kids around you like in in
whatever way for whatever reason and
it's I I feel the same way about that I
feel completely the same way about that
there's something that um triggers you
to just have to like take on
responsibility in AIDs that you wouldn't
think you'd have to right and like in
doing that I think that parents in
inherently the child is a burden on them
like they don't know how much
responsibility they are they just know
that like they are a CH they're just a
child right and parents have to children
children
as at least from my experience um they
have to view children as like a as a
burden as as something that they are
responsible for and so like talking to
them about them in front of them is very
much like yeah we want to include them
but also like we don't have [__] time
for that [__] we to [__] figure
out how we're gonna feed this little
bastard you know like how are we gonna
feed it we don't know what it wants we
don't care what it wants we don't need
to be a part of this conversation
because it's not going to be able to
work and bring home the money you know
it's interesting to think like that and
I I wonder like talking back to like
this the generational differences in
like parenting um you know we're very
much
a a lot of our peers are very much a
product of like the um the
the oh God what do you call it the
trophy for showing up generation you
know um the participation award
generation right we got Pat On The Backs
because we showed up and we're very like
coddled in a lot of ways and you kind of
still see a lot of that um you know
we're also the generation of like people
getting cancelled because they got uh
recorded um smacking their baby at a
Walmart right and at the end of the day
I don't have kids I don't know what it's
like to raise kids but I can tell you
right now maybe sometimes your baby
needs to be smacked I don't know I don't
know I'm sure the urg there to your
babybody yeah doing it to Walmart in
front of everybody maybe that's not the
way to do it but like nobody wants to go
and um nobody wants to go and and and
make their child into like the traumatic
version of their own childhood yeah yeah
well I think when it comes to when it
comes to being a parent there is these
you know it's funny I just mentioned
like there's these two separates that
are confusing for a child of like the
these realities of
um you know like
you know we're watching TV but I'm also
watching us watch TV there's kind of
like these sep
so the kid as much as truth is one of
the most important things and it really
needs to be like the the the fulcrum of
how you how
you raise anybody let alone an adult
raising a kid there's a level where my
kid doesn't need to know that every bite
of food he eats gives me stress about
paying bills that month
um something that I think you know we've
talked a little bit about trauma like we
all have our own trauma something that
my my parents did um that affected me
later on um and and again like I love my
my mom and dad very much like we've
we've worked through a lot of these
things and I'm not saying this to like
hold anything over of them they're
wonderful people and they're very
self-reflective about these things now
too but so like I was um a condom
ripping baby so I was an accident and
like my mom in her Young unaware State
you know she's early early 20s like mid
20s whatever she would constantly say
things like you were an accident baby
you were an accident we didn't we didn't
want you we didn't we didn't plan to
have you and so I internalize these
things and like now I still do with
self- worth issues and like um being a
burden on people is huge I grew up my
teenage years um I I would like live
with friends for for a few times during
the week and um I was always very aware
like I'm another mouth to feed like
these I didn't earn this food but paying
their own money and feeding me and I'm
just always really aware of being a
burden on people
um I think there's a way now that we
would realize of being parents where
it's not that I need to lie to my kid
and tell them hey we're rich like we've
got like I know you don't see a pool in
the backyard but like pretend that you
see a pool in the backyard like you know
you're not lying to your kid but there's
a way of I don't need to know that we're
going to we're kind of struggling to pay
the electricity bill like when I'm 6
years old I don't need to know about
about the bills so I think there's a
level of being truthful with your kid
but also creating this world where they
can play I think a you know a good
parent successfully does this and again
if you know don't beat yourself up if
you're not successfully doing this I
know it must be more difficult than I
could put into words but
like there's a way that your child needs
to have this
illusion of them just exploring the
world like they you need to until
they're 18 they need to not even know
about bills as far as I'm concerned they
need to not know about the electricity
they they don't need to think that they
were an accident in any sort of way you
know that's why I man I don't know how I
don't know how people raise a kid or
have a marriage without without God I
mean and I'm not trying to like say a
Dei or I'm not trying to strike just
Christianity or anything but like things
like faith and um um trust and like
knowing that everything's going to be
okay like those things I don't really
know how do you contact those very
important things of like you know just
living a human life let alone raising
raising a young adult to have standards
and values and and you know a successful
life when they're on their own I don't
know how you absolutely you tune into
those things without some form of God or
higher power just some sort of system
you know it's interesting that you bring
it up because it's something that we
have both talked about like on our walks
like one of the last walk runs that we
did we talked about what it would be
like to have like a spiritual type of
like conversation or or a group group
like somewhat of a men's group somewhat
of a um something to to connect with
each other and to talk about these
Concepts and what they mean something
that like in I think the way I phrase it
or the way that I personally view it is
um I don't currently have any sort of
belief system into like a um into a
traditional religion I would say um and
so for me it's
like I've always wondered like not
always but the the question of like code
like a moral code has always
been something that I that I Ponder and
even like a lot of times in my
journal I try to like I like simple
things I like just simple words to to
describe a code I don't want to have
like long paragraphs and um you know
like I don't want to like a whole like
Constitution for how I want to live my
life but more of just like if I can
narrow it down into like something that
I could say less than 10 words you know
and I think some of the things that I
that I write down in the mornings the
the the current ones that I've decided
are the closest thing to a moral code
that I personally have is like courage
acceptance love patience uh truth Andor
honesty um and I think there's one
more but that's that's the gist of it
right there um
and by not having any sort
of
community or even like like
organization that reinforces those
things specifically through like Parable
through like written word whatever you
want to call it through like agreeance
on uh on on these Concepts and what they
mean for all of us and how they always
change specifically through life like
I'm imagining myself back in um Catholic
Church as a child like listening to the
pares and most of the time not paying
attention but every once in a while
something grabbing me and being like wow
that actually makes a lot of sense and I
do actually believe that you know you
should be good to your neighbor you know
things like that you shouldn't help out
someone in need or oh this guy's tire is
flat on the side of the road why
wouldn't I take the time to stop and
help him like my I really don't have
anywhere to be that bad you know so I
didn't silence my phone but
um the thought of not having something
like that um particularly when raising a
family is um it's something that I've
always said I've always said if I have
kids I'm going to take them to I'm going
to go to church
right I don't know where I don't know
what church but I was like I've always
said like there's so much to be said
about having a community that all
believes in like similar values um that
gets together regularly that talks
openly that has trust in each other um
that ideally you would like have some
donuts with because who doesn't want
donuts on a like all of those things I
remember going to church and like liking
a lot of those things about it but being
raised Catholic I specifically remember
the day that I looked around and
everybody was like singing in hymns and
and whatnot and I
was just really turned off I was very
like something about it just made me
realize we're all just followers nobody
there is a leader and we're all
following something that I didn't
actually believe because I was like at
that point I hadn't read the Bible but I
had listened to enough of it to know
that it wasn't you know realistic and so
in my head I was like okay well why are
we all just blatantly following this
thing and nobody's really asking
questions at least the questions that I
think are important and if we do ask
those questions they're pretty much
answered like non- ansers you know um so
I think that it would be a lot easier to
swallow the concept of spirituality and
religion in general um if there were
solutions to those those
those questions that I'm Pro posing
right now you know yeah yeah well I I
think a lot of
those you you hear the term baby you
know throwing out the baby with the bath
water you hear that when it comes to
religion and God and spirituality and I
think that is really like a big core of
what of what goes on there is uh you
know dudes like us have those
experiences where you look around you're
like oh I don't like there was parts of
this that I resonated with but like
overall you guys are having a different
experience than me here you know like I
don't know I wish that I could believe
everything y'all are apparently
believing but I don't so what do I do
with that I had times when I was young
where um
uh I wasn't I wasn't like raised in like
a Christian background or anything um I
feel like my parents are probably more
more more apt to like poke fun at it
more than anything there wasn't really
much uh now my parents would say
probably they claim more of like a my
mom's side would play more of like a
pagan um version of spirituality but um
there was times where I went and I would
go with like a girlfriend or something
girlfriend's family and I would leave
going okay well I'm burning in Hell
according to these people like I'm I'm
[__] like I I would leave just not
feeling good about anything and going
according to these people I am like just
I might as well set myself on fire right
now because that's where I'm heading you
know and so that wasn't that didn't give
me any of the answers that that I that I
looked for but I also had these very um
it was just like a common response to
any anything to do with religion or
spirituality like I just had like such a
reaction to it of you know when I hear
words like Faith or trust or whatever I
have all these preconceived ideas and
all these like like I don't even let
those words in when the word God Lord
God is so scary to so many people yeah
so yeah our body just tends up like oh
don't you tell me about a a giant man in
the clouds like don't you talk about
this deity you know of like
but but I I think um if we give
ourselves if if we let ourselves really
explore what that stuff means for us
personally and I don't even mean like us
personally in a conversation with a
pastor if that's how you get there
that's cool but like us personally as in
you read this you're by yourself in your
room and you read this stuff like what
does it really feel like within you like
what does it really mean to you you know
I think we should all be given
permission and the tools and um the amp
ification from one another to explore
spirituality as individuals like being a
human we all like there's you know eight
billion humans each of us should have
our own relationship individual
relationship with God or or a Jesus or a
Buddha or Avatar whatever it is like you
know there's layers um not to deity not
to just make things a deity but um we
have like a language there dude there's
Pathways in our brain there you know
you've heard the term godsize whole
there's something within us of being a
human in the human psyche that has room
the puzzle pie puzzle pieces for like
God and spirit and the soul and um like
yeah you're a part of this family and
you work at a grocery store and your
employee badge says Frank but also
you're at one with everything you know
like like there's there's
paradoxically room for all of it and we
should all I'm I'm getting on such a
rambling Sid Sprint I'm sorry cam I love
it I love it yeah um but yeah I just I
think there's a lot of baby with the
bath water that happens there and um I
hope dudes dudes like us like dudes our
age having more of these public
conversations kind of points things
within each other of like man if if the
the people around you or the way that
you learned about these things didn't
work for you or you know you're you're
in these rooms looking around going oh
I'm not resonating with what you guys
are resonating with that doesn't mean
dump the word God and never look up look
it up again or slam the Bible shut and
never open it I think it means you've
now been invited on a self-exploration
journey that maybe none of these people
have the answer for you and maybe the
answer is this is a door that opens from
the inside you know so we should all we
we all have that it's it's part of Being
Human we all have a spiritual journey
and nobody tells us what that looks like
that's all for our for our own selves to
experience and it it does bring me back
to us talking about um like a format of
a format of
conversation um that Austin is such a
hot bed
of new psychology these days Austin's
such a hot bed of like new ideas taking
hold and like openness to them and
people just very very interested in um
what all these other super [__]
interesting people are doing in their
City I I think I honestly after
traveling around so much I honestly see
Austin
being the
next the next San Francisco but not the
next Silicon Valley but not for Tech the
next LA but not just for um fashion and
and culture next New York but not just
for art I mean philosophical spiritual
aspect to it there's something here that
is not and I'm not even there I'm in
Moab and I can feel it just in our
conversation it's rad there's something
there that is
just it just draws people in like I've
listened to a couple podcasts the last
few days and like brne brown lives in
freaking Austin like know that of course
yes very cool very cool do um I sent
that podcast the other day about those
guys that were talking about like
anthropology and kind of like I would
say there's some geopolitics mixed in um
but both of them were like history Andor
anthropology guys uh that were talking
about like how America could be like 11
different culture uh countries based on
like culture and based on history and
why they moved why different religions
and different people moved into
different places and both of them
singled out Austin and both of them they
both live in Texas one of them both
definitely lives in Austin and both of
them singled out Texas as basically
being able to be its own country because
it's not similar to any of these other
like 11 Colony countries they're talking
about for a lot of reasons and
specifically Austin as much as they
talked about like LA and New York being
its own type of like culture and its own
City and something that um you would
almost consider like Paris France as its
own City and like uh even like Fran or
like Munich Germany how like those two
places are not really like any other
place in the world Tokyo um obviously I
put I would put New York in there I
would definitely put La in there and
these guys are saying that Austin is
right in there with them same as Miami
um those play like they are not like any
other place in the world and to say that
like there's not um that the interesting
thing about this podcast was talking
about how they don't um see a lot of
like Americans and westerners taking uh
hold of their own culture taking like
pride in their culture Texas is a
outlier in that Texas culture and Texas
is a big deal now as much as I love the
state of Texas I say that I'm from
Austin when I go places I love being a
Texan I love having pride in being a
Texan but I take even more pride in
being from Austin yeah seriously I don't
say Texas I say Austin specifically yes
because and there are people flocking
here from all over the world and it's
not just because it's cool originally I
thought it was just because it's cool so
much more than that and so curious to
see where it goes like even to the like
it's almost like how these Mormons call
Salt Lake and Utah they Zion like
there's something about Austin that is
like I don't want it like that's kind of
a crazy relation there but uh there is
something about it that the new age of
um like kind of like a lesser ego and
like a more um I don't know man there's
there's a friendliness to Austin that LA
and New York don't have there's a pride
and a proudness of it that like the
medwest the Midwest doesn't have there's
a Like Love Thy Neighbor aspect to it
that really nowhere else in the country
has that's very very Tech and there's
something very open to new ideas the
rest of Texas and a lot of the basically
everything east of the Mississippi
doesn't have yeah think that are a very
cool conglomerate of all these things
together and and I am personally
incredibly excited to see where it goes
yeah I I I think uh I was just thinking
to add to add to that I I think um
something that I was drawn to is kind of
like the the punk rockness which also I
I think if you want to interlay the word
punk rock with cowboy I think that
actually makes a lot of sense like
Cowboys are punk as like they're doing
it their own way they're making the path
they're like oh there's there's no Trail
here I'm going to [__] make the trail
myself you know um the cowboy punk rock
is I was really drawn towards that and I
also was thinking you know at the
beginning of a conversation cam we were
we were you know mentioning Travis
Pastrana he did the first backflip on a
on a
Motocross on an MX bike I think there's
something about Austin that like there's
a lot of edge pushers here like like the
edge you know all the comedians who are
moving here which is you know that's a
whole another chapter of like funny
philosophy and we need comedians like
they're very important um I don't want
to modificate comedians that can get so
dorky but really them this turning into
like the comedy Hub of the world of the
Free Speech kind of Hub of the world uh
again all this sounds so dorky to name
but there is something about like people
across the US are looking at Austin and
like we keep breaking the four-minute
mile and people are like dude I need to
go there and like break my four-minute
mile you know and I think me as a
Creator I don't really know it's hard
for me to I've been almost 5 years here
it's hard for me to put my finger on
exactly but I was drawn to that like
there is some sort of um at the edge of
like I said you know being a poet being
an artist being a a
musician I I want to push the edges of
what it means to be just a human a
person um and it feels like this is a
playground for that there's people to my
left and right you know and every yoga
class I go to there's someone who is
also just exploring the depths of their
Consciousness all the stage t I work
with like you know they're out here
making 20 bucks an hour and eating
garbage food but they're also like if I
listen to their album they just put out
yesterday they're a brilliant musician
you know there's all these people who
are just pushing the
boundaries of what they're doing um I'll
add that you have that in other places
but there's not like that uh you have
that
um the thought like Denver is kind of
this funny place where everybody goes to
find themsel right but it's very cold
it's a very cold Community like Denver
is not open to me to me it's not very
open it's not very friendly um it's very
like uh in a lot of ways it's kind of
fake Austin doesn't feel that way Austin
feels warm and welcoming and very much
you feel like you're a part of it you
don't feel like you're you're
surrounding the outside of it you don't
feel like you're an afterthought or even
just like um you don't really feel like
you're you're an outcast it feels like
everyone can be a part of something here
I love that about it I love that you can
feel like you are in the community and
maybe I am biased because I from there
pretty much I've been there since I was
you know five six years old but even
when I leave and come back I it takes me
like a day or two to like refind it but
I'm immediately reimmersed in what feels
so real and so friendly I well I mean I
I was very like how we met we met
through through floon you were working
at floon and um I mean I was I felt
instantly part of the community there I
mean you definitely had a hand in that
just I it's it's a gift you have earlier
we were talking about are different
gifts you know a mother shows up as a
mother so well like yours is we we've
spoken about this off off camera but
like yours part of yours is definitely
bringing people together the community
aspect is is part of you uh making
people feel feel comfortable and welcome
and um you're really good at like
bringing out the best in people and then
bringing them all into one place and
then like I feel like a picture you put
your hands on your hips and like all
right go I know you're all
awesome like you have that skill um and
so I I got to experience that too but so
this is something we've talked to we're
getting a little bit up here in time cam
but I think it'd be cool to kind of
round about on this community thing you
know we're both in Austin we're both you
know we're born in 91 we we're around
the same age
we've talked about this a few times like
we've met up doing like kind of running
club things um we' both agreed man
there's a for this mix
terribly yeah I know I can't wait yeah
can't wait till get back we're gonna
have to end it again but um I know I
think uh putting our money where our
mouth is you know I've talked I'm really
want I got my met mindfulness meditation
teacher certification I want to do
something with it if I can be useful I
want I want you know I I I want the the
puppet of the universe to to put his
hand up my butt and and use me as a
puppet you know use me for good so um I
I want to try to contribute to this
community so I guess I I think it'd be
cool to end this cam with like a
brainstorm of um how do we use this
awesomeness of Austin
and this presentness of us being dudes
without you know we specifically don't
have kids we're looking for meaning we
know the spiritual stuff is helpful we
know like mindfulness meditation all
that sort of stuff is helpful we feel
better when we link up with people and
do physical activity or make friend
groups or communities do we start doing
a once a week thing do we do a zoom call
do we meet up twice a week to go running
like how do we make action out of our
ideas and um capitalize on the momentum
of like this this community thing trying
to be built through us like how do we
not stop it how do we add to this thing
trying to you know grow through US
absolutely I mean I I
will obvious ly I will uh address my uh
my main drawback which is my location is
I'm just not there for for a while which
is a biggest bummer because ideally I
would say we just go start a meet up and
just start doing something um where we
get a few people together and have like
somewhat of a spiritual conversation
over a walk with like a Sit afterwards
and what I was imagining earlier um when
talking
about uh um religion and like a moral
code and things like that like what it
means to me I basically imagine
like somewhat of a leaderless like AA
format of you know we're not necessarily
trying to heal any specific trauma um
we're not trying to like keep anybody
from jumping off a bridge there's
there's other resources for that but I
think it's more of how do you
intentionally want to positively move
forward with your life
and how can we all share in ways that we
want to do that and how can we all share
in the reasons why we find ourselves
here how can we all share like our
beliefs of how we want to live our
day-to- day because if that was like a
weekly reminder to me if there was
something that I was able to to look
into my own perspective and like I think
both of us are great storytellers I
think you're an excellent Storyteller
one of I mean one of your greatest gifts
and greatest traits is being able to get
other people to tell stories too and I
think that I am super um open to sharing
and open to telling my stories and I
even like hold myself to a higher
standard of telling them because when
I'm around you I feel I feel that I feel
like I'm lifted up by uh by your company
in that way um so I think if people are
we find folks that that are interested
in that folks that are interested in
sharing and why um they want to be a
part of something and and we can share
ourselves and and the thought of uh
taking a walk around the lake and having
a few a few people in on that or even
having like individual groups like you
break people up if it's big enough and
you say you guys go over here and you go
over here and we go over here and
whatever and say if you have like I
don't know like think of like a child's
care like a Kids Care Facility like 1 to
7 1 to eight something like that for
everybody that does it I guess that's
kind of like bigger picture but ideally
having like a regular weekly Meetup um
where we go for a walk and then
afterwards like have a talk and just
talk about like what life is and what
life has been and where we're at and why
we feel the way we
do in my head that sounds like a great
idea maybe we just try it and see what
happens yeah dude I think it's yeah it
sounds so yeah like and it really
doesn't have to be super structured I
feel like we successfully just by
talking about the things we're
inevitably interested in and want to
talk about I mean like you said I feel
like every time we meet up we end up in
the spiritual realm of conversation it's
just what's fun you know it's it's
what's adventurous and what's what's
right there you know it's it's it's
right there on the surface to to to be
plucked out I um there's this term and I
kept hearing it in my head as you were
talking um creating a
container and and like it sounds it
sounds kind of cheap but it is perfect
like how could we create a container
once a week it's nothing too crazy you
don't have to sign anywhere you don't
have to do an NDA like you could be
anybody you could be going through
anything you don't have to wear anything
or you know rep us or whatever like it's
just we're going to be here at this time
talking about this stuff come on in you
know okay absolutely absolutely and I
even it's interesting because we talked
about I wondered if there's anything
else out there there was I saw on
Instagram the other day it looked super
cheesy but maybe that's just what this
is um it was something like called like
meditation Bros or meditation
dude you know what I'm talking about
have you seen this no but I it's
probably specifically targeted to me
because of our conversations I'm sure uh
but it was like an Instagram
advertisement of like sign up and come
and join us we're a bunch of bros that
like to get together and like meditate
talk about life and [__] and well
clearly Bros are desperate for this
stuff man I mean let's let's be honest
like there's a lot of people who are not
even just males but like dude a lot of
us are lonely as all [__] yeah a lot of
us
humans we we're just looking for
something real too you know I mean we're
we're entrenched in reality TV versions
of everything that's going on whether
it's politics or you know the
geopolitical [__] or um just just
entertainment in general actual reality
TV you know it's like everything is
Kardashian ified and so for us to to
link up and be able to set our armor
down without the judgment and just like
hey man I'm having a human experience
aren't you and the other person's like
yeah dud dude like that's what we need
you know me too absolutely absolutely I
think there's something to be said about
um having like a premise of of why you
get together you know and I I don't know
what exactly a premise could be but
whether it's just connection you know
because I can tell you right now
starting my day with this conversation
with you is going to set me off on a on
a trajectory uh that's going to be
different than yesterday you know um
just being able to share with you and be
able to to connect with you on such a
level is going to make me just feel good
all day long it's like we are
connecting uh we're we're connected
individuals we seek connection we love
to connect something about like laughter
like laughter is not for yourself like
laughter is for connection right and
love it it makes you feel good so like
why wouldn't you do it kind of thing you
know so I wonder like how much we could
take that into it and say how well can
we just connect with one another what if
it is literally just like we get
together and we sit around and we talk
to each other and that's what we do it's
like we have like a one-on-one like
setting of like you know you just have
conversations with people and connect
and then you share about what do you
think um what do you what are you
thinking right now and you share with
like in a group setting it's like you go
from a one-on-one to a group and then
just see where it goes yeah I mean I
there's the there's a saying in the
meditative world uh yoga specifically
Namaste you've heard heard that and it
and it means the light in me sees and
honors the light in you and I think that
by us creating containers or holding
space um and just sharing like what's
going on within us or like hey here's
some things I'm going through suddenly
it shines a light or allows space for
the light of someone else to take the
stage like suddenly you know someone
might show up they were not even
thinking about these things they were
not planning on talking about them but
like here I am sharing about my
childhood trauma and soing they're like
they feel okay to talk about theirs and
suddenly they just process something
they did not even realize they wanted to
process needed to process but there was
room for it and so they they showed up
and and suddenly now that thing that
maybe he's been plagg them for 20 years
has just been vocalized and their body
feels a little bit lighter you know so I
think the the The Light in Me loves and
and gives permission to light in you
whatever it is yeah just just by showing
up and living authentically or living or
just sharing what the hell we're going
through as a human it opens the space
for the person the other people around
you know it really does yes dude I just
had a rad idea yeah okay what about this
here's like another like uh it's just
like a taper off of this I guess or like
a
sidearm what if specifically because you
and I are both in the event industry
where like we can find ourselves in
other places and and wondering like
where we fit in what we're doing
whatever what if we had had some sort of
Meetup that was like for that reason
like the thought of having something
where it's like we almost like aren't
even dependent or don't even really care
how local you are we're specifically
targeting like you aren't local or
you're just here for a day or you're in
the event business or you're here for a
week or you're a traveling nurse and you
don't have anybody or whatever it is so
good I love this typically angling
towards like people that just don't have
anybody to connect to you know yeah yeah
how cool would that be it's like you
find a way to like Bridge connections
with people that like we have been in
that like it's coming from a place of
servitude where like you and I have both
been in another place like me right now
in this strange land where I don't know
anybody here and my connection like my
day is going to change because the
connection I'm having with you right now
how much you do that on like a weekly
basis with like other people in the city
people that just they don't have anybody
to connect with and they don't have any
um they don't have any friends or
whatever it is and you just start with
that like how cool would that be to say
you know this is like we're benefiting
we're we're trying to like serve from a
place that we've all been at before yeah
yeah I I heard man I heard this term
this morning the room is not the room it
just makes me think of like um uh I'm
sorry I'm trying to sew too many things
into this but like yeah like a a
Community without a place like a a
floating Community like the community is
like we're creating an in-person
Community but we all travel so like the
the meeting spot's never the same um the
time and space is never the same but
like our uh we we all travel and we
create this like we create this space
when we decide we all have this thing we
want to accomplish together and we meet
up and suddenly that thing is
is is is sprouted I mean it makes me
think of like dude because I travel a
lot too for work and in the event
industry the way to connect is drinking
unfortunately that's like it's a big
part of our in the event World um you
know so sometimes more than less and I'm
not just saying like it's a bunch of
Alcoholics or anything but it really is
like and after you work 18 hour days
it's nice to have a beer you know and I
haven't drank for a couple years myself
but like I still there is instances of
that just shedding the day and being
able to just BS with your co-workers
about whatever went on that day or even
not even talk about work and just Bond
and and you know complaint or whatever
it is with with the people you're you're
traveling with or at a hotel bar
whatever it is is is nice but you know
you like me you know I don't drink
anymore and so I I avoid those areas
like I don't even want to go have you
know fries and a burger or whatever like
I just don't even want to be around it I
end up just putting headphones on and
having like a a spiritual practice to
recharge on my own but if if there's a
container we could create or um
encourage other other people to create
on their own too of a place to meet up
that's not just drinking when you're
traveling I think inevitably it'll be
spiritual you know I think it be R man
what if it is something like in this
format too what if it is some sort of um
it could be a um wow it could be like a
zoom format it could be a uh like a
digital format as well I guess it
doesn't have to be in person you know
even just for you and I and um for any
anyone else in the same person position
um I don't know how that would look or
how that would work especially you know
just because of uh time uh schedules and
and things like that but yeah that's
another that's another thing to look at
too so I mean I I think putting our
putting a best foot forward to making it
happen not saying like Hey we're going
to start this and now going forward
every Sunday at 2 pm we do this like you
know we don't have access to that right
now but I think leaving this
conversation with the intention
intention of of trying to sprout that
and then
going forward I think I would just like
to even with my my recent meditation
t-shir certification stuff I would like
to
um not that I want to like lead all
these things all the time like I think
there's a way for me to maybe connect us
maybe I could guide us through a quick
little meditation then I would love to
like just be another person and not um
you know I'm not I'm not fully prepared
to start my cult at this time I have a
lot of paperwork to do before I start a
CT so dang d s great uh but yeah yeah I
love this man I think I think that's so
cool I think there's a lot of room for
this and I think there's uh we'll
probably find that you know there'll be
some fellas and ladies alike listening
to this part of the podcast that will be
like hell yeah that sounds really cool
so we should dive more into this man 100
perc 100 perc rad I've got so it's I I
do need to go and I think that we are at
time much but um I have so many more
ideas now than I had in hour ago and so
yeah I'll be calling you later on yeah
that sounds good too well man we'll to
do podcasts more often like like I said
I I love talking to you it's always
always a pleasure man so anytime you
have like a Wellspring of ideas that you
want to get out to the world hit me up
and we'll schedule podcast man I always
love talking to you absolutely I would
love to yeah I uh Kim thank you so much
man thank you for for doing this we've
been talking about getting a podcast on
for a while there'll be many more I'm
sure um thank you for allowing the the
free flow just hang out part of things
like uh it was very fulfilling to me it
was so fun hanging out with you man I
had I am so grateful that you even asked
me to do it I feel embarrassed to say
that I hadn't even really looked at your
podcast until like the last night and I
started looking I was like oh my God
he's got like over a 100 episodes he's
got a bunch of people on here I was like
I feel so grateful to be even asked for
this you know um I really really
appreciate it and uh it's given me an
outlet uh to share in this morning that
I never would have thought of um and uh
yeah man I I love the connection that
you and I share and I love uh the the
the ideas that we can both just kind of
like free base and just not have to
worry about where they go it's it's very
enlightening to to know um that you know
we haven't known each other for that
long the connection that we have is
pretty rad um so yeah uh great stuff man
and um yeah I'd love to share some more
ideas with you later on yeah absolutely
man yeah I'm grateful for I'm grateful
for our connection and and how we met
and um really like the whole community
of of homies around you that I've got to
like you know meet and and interact with
and um it's made my time in Austin
incredibly valuable so I'm grateful for
grateful for your friendship man this
was really cool hell yeah well I
appreciate everything Jacob yeah well uh
listeners you know the drill if you
haven't drank any water at this point in
your day what are you doing dude drink
some water get hydrated if you haven't
stretched today stretch out move around
move that fascia get movement get
outside if you haven't got side love
yourself um if you want to hear more
from cam comment below um cam if you'd
like I can include your your Instagram
and whatnot in in the description reach
out to questions and uh yeah I guess
we'll we'll see you next time that be
right hey do me a favor and Link that um
that personality test in there because
I'm curious about that yeah yeah
everybody uh look below it'll be I think
it'll be the mbti uh I think that's what
it what it's for but regardless yeah
it's like the infj ENFP uh whatever
whatever uh it's it's it's valuable when
I first learned about I'm just
continually going I'm sorry uh when I
first learned about it it was like a
pretty much brought me to tears moment
for me personally some someone who like
deeply wants to understand himself um
and when I read the synopsis like took
the test a couple times it gave me the
thing here's what you are here's how you
think bro for me when I was reading it
it was like deeply moving I was like
I've never felt so seen by any text
before this moment so anyway I'll
include that check it out do the thing
below and um C love you buddy we'll see
you next time absolutely love you too
buddy have a bad dayat
[Music]
brother knowledge is
power reality
[Music]
is junkyard love podcast